Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ketan-patel-522b6745 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Channel

Business Strategy
Business Development

Languages

Gujarati,Marathi,HIndi (Limited Working)

English (Full Professional)

Ketan Patel

Chairman and Managing director at Creative Peripherals and Distributions Limited

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Summary

Experienced Chief Executive Officer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer hardware industry. Skilled in Marketing Management, Business Planning, E-commerce, Entrepreneurship, with an interest in startups and technology. Successfully founded and listed businesses.

Experience

Creative Peripherals and Distribution Limited. Founder Director & Ceo August 1992 - Present Mumbai Area, India

xpress computers
Customer Support Engineer
May 1989 - June 1991 (2 years 2 months)

Education

Vidya vardhini polytechnic Computer technology , Computer Technology/Computer Systems Technology · (1987 - 1999)

G H High School

Indian Institute of Management Bangalore
Master of Business Administration - MBA